目 前 資 金
最 新 余 額
人人影視
YYeTs.com
原創翻譯  雙語字幕
僅供學習 禁止用于任何商業盈利行為
更多影視更新
請登陸www.YYeTs.com
打工
姐妹花
第十集
第三季
打工
姐妹花
第十集
第三季
翻校  泡面大廚賽太公
翻校  泡糊小廚YY貓
后期 泡泡親愛的灰灰
時間軸 總監  泡糊小廚YY貓
麥克斯  我知道新時間表該怎么排了
Okay, Max, I figured out our new schedule.
我也才知道我們用的便宜牙膏
And I figured out the cheap toothpaste
其實是放尿布疹軟膏
we've been using is really diaper cream.
但好歹我牙齦上的尿布疹都消了
On the plus side, that rash cleared up on my gums.
晚上6點到清晨2點在餐廳上班
We'll do our diner shift from 6:00 till 2:00,
清晨2點到清晨4點賣小蛋糕
then sell cupcakes here from 2:00 to 4:00,
早上7點到11點做小蛋糕
make the cupcakes in the morning from 7:00 to 11:00,
然后中午12點到下午4點去學校
And then pastry school from 12:00 to 4:00.
-有忘了什么嗎  -拉屎跟睡覺時間
- Forget anything? - Just poopin' and sleepin'.
現在我得去重安排時間表了
Now, I have to go rewrite the schedule.
來吧  麥克斯  明天是你的超超大日子
Let's go, Max, you have a huge, huge day tomorrow.
第一天上烘焙學校
First day of pastry school.
別說"超超大"了
Stop saying it's huge.
每次以為要看到"超大東西"時
Whenever I think something's gonna be huge,
最后都只看到"大巨蛋"
It just turns out to be all balls.
我花錢干洗了我的襯衫
I splurged and had my blouse cleaned.
這干洗袋讓我想起了當有錢人的時光
Dry cleaning bags remind me of when I had money.
那袋子只讓我回想起
Really? They remind me of
我媽曾想把我悶死
when my mother tried to suffocate me.
據說而已啦  走吧
Allegedly. Let's go.
等等  麥克斯  你還不能走
Wait, wait. Max, you can't go yet.
我需要你留下來幫忙一件事
I need you to stay and help with something.
阿憨  我都教過你了
Han, I told you-- it's bend and wipe,
彎下身擦屁股  褲子拉上穿穿好
then up come your big boy pants.
阿憨說得對  你不能走
Yeah, Han's right. You can't go.
再待一會吧
Stay here a few more minutes.
為啥
Why?
我們要開麥克斯的批斗大會嗎
Are we having an intervention for Max?
大家安安
Hey, everybody.
我還沒錯過"歡慶麥克斯
Oh, I hope I'm not late for Max's
首日上學驚喜派對"吧
first day of school surprise party.
蘇菲  我們都還沒給她驚喜呢
Sophie, we hadn't surprised her yet.
她站在這都聽見啦
Oh, but she's right there.
驚喜都被你劇透光了  阿憨
You just blew it, Han.
有驚喜派對呢
Aw, a surprise party.
-是不是很溫馨啊  麥克斯  -我才不信咧
- Isn't this sweet, Max? - I don't trust it.
上次奧列格給過我"驚喜"
Last time Oleg yelled "surprise" at me,
他把雞雞塞在熱狗面包中間了
his penis was on a hot dog bun.
一盒肉香滿溢披薩
One meat lover's pizza.
一位肉欲滿溢愛人
And one meat lover.
麥克斯  快來  "趁熱享用"哦
Max, come on. Get it while it's hot.
你去打開那盒子
You're opening that box.
誰有十塊錢
Hm, who's got a ten
給這個可愛的送披薩男小費啊
to tip the cute pizza delivery guy?
蘇菲  他是路易斯  白班服務生
Sophie, this is Luis, the day waiter.
你就是蘇菲啊
Oh, you're Sophie,
奧列格的前任
Oleg's ex.
姐妹  我對你了如指掌
Sister, I know all about you.
真的咩
Oh, do you?
你真的對我從里到外都了解嗎
Do you know all about me?
我是他的好朋友
I'm his good friend.
你的口音有點重  我聽不太清楚
You know, I'm having trouble hearing your accent.
是"好朋友"還是"女"朋友啊
Did you say "good friend" or "girlfriend?"
拜托  我倒想呢
Please, mami. I wish.
我喜歡這娛樂節目啊
I like the entertainment.
比我朋友妮妮16歲生日派對上的魔朮師好
It's better than the magician at my friend Stephanie's 16th birthday
他把我朋友的貞操變沒了
that made her virginity disappear.
麥克斯  我們都以你為傲
Max, we're all so proud of you.
明天是你后半生的第一天
Tomorrow is the first day of the rest of your life.
靠  我又得再活一遍啊
Aw, crap. I gotta do this again?
行  但是這次
All right, but this time,
我不要再看勵志電影了
I'm not seeing Trouble With the Curve.
你即將要干一番大事業
You are about to do something very big.
對啊  向前邁大步
Yes, she is. Such a big step.
我們一起邁進一大步
Big step for both of us,
因為我也得用我的商業頭腦
'cause I'll be using my business acumen
在辦公室里工作來幫她賺學費
working in the office to help pay the tuition.
別吵  我是在說麥克斯呢
Shh. I'm talking about Max.
我們大家都湊錢給你買禮物
So we all chipped in to get you something
慶祝你首日上學
for your first day of school.
-也是我的第一天  -卡洛琳  拜托了
- It's my first day too. - Caroline, please,
你害我聽不到阿憨說麥克斯什么了
I can't hear Han talking about Max, okay?
給  小寶貝
Here you go, darling,
上學的書包
A book bag for school.
所以給我的驚喜派對是在這之后嗎
So what, then? Is my surprise party after this one?
這是怎么一回事
What is happening?
有人笑容滿面地對我好
People doing nice things for me and smiling?
是不是又要換寄養家庭了
Am I transferring foster homes again?
里面還有別的東西哦
And there's more stuff inside.
你又把驚喜先劇透出來了
That was supposed to be a surprise too.
驚喜吧
Oh. Surprise!
麥克斯  打開  看看里面東西
Max, open it. Look inside.
對啊  麥克斯  看看里面有啥
Yeah, Max, see what's inside for your big day.
麥克斯的大日子  也是我的大日子哦
Big day for Max. Big day for me as well.
一張交通卡  不是吧
A metrocard? No way.
我送的  無限乘坐哦
From me. Unlimited rides.
無限"騎"[乘坐]嗎
Oh. Unlimited rides?
你屁股上的騷貨紋身是這個嗎
Is that what your tramp stamp says?
本來要跟你吵的  但你這吐槽實在是妙
I was gonna get mad, but that was a damn good one.
這又是啥  阿憨的房子嗎
What's this? Han's house?
你簡單說句"謝謝"就夠了
A simple "thank you" would suffice.
謝謝你送我你的房子  阿憨
Thank you for your house, Han.
鉛筆盒  我好喜歡啊
It's a pencil case, and I love it.
我剛才還干坐在這  想著你們會不會
And I was sitting here, thinking how you were
忘了明天也是我的大日子呢
all ignoring my part of the big day.
然后你們就送了我這個
And then, you give me this pencil case
帶去上班用的鉛筆盒  証明我想錯了
to use in the office and prove me wrong.
那是送麥克斯的
That's for Max.
你們他媽腦子是哪有問題啊
What the hell is wrong with you people?
麥克斯都不需要用鉛筆
Max doesn't even need pencils.
她會在烘焙東西
She'll be baking.
她是會暈乎乎[烘焙]才對
Well, she'll be baked.
打開看看
Take a look.
大麻煙
Joints.
厄爾  你真是太好了
Earl, that's so sweet.
這一盒夠我抽到今天休息時間了
These should last me till recess.
等等  蘇菲要送的繡名廚師制服呢
Wait, where's the Chef's coat Sophie had monogrammed?
阿憨  這是我要送的驚喜呢
Han, that was supposed to be a surprise.
我故意的  報應來了吧
Oh, I know. Karma's a bitch.
好吧
Oh, well.
給
Look.
上面有我名字呢
My name's on this.
唯一上面有過我名字的東西
the only thing my name's ever been on before
是驗毒尿檢杯
is a urine sample.
謝謝你們大家
Thank you, everyone.
所以那書包里沒一樣東西是給我的嗎
So there is nothing in that bag for me?
毛都沒有嗎
Nothing?
現在如果送我奧列格的雞雞熱狗  我都愿意收下
I'd even take Oleg's penis in a hot dog bun right now.
馬上給你做
I'll be right back.
-要上車啦  -請讓讓
- Getting on. - Please move.
-上車啦  -讓讓啊
-姐要上車  -拜托讓讓
- Getting on. - Please move.
-上啦  -讓啊
- On! - Move!
-上  上  -讓  讓
- On! On! - Move! Move!
我愛死地鐵了
I love the subway.
發泄怒氣的完美地點
It's the perfect place to get out aggression.
我剛才錘了一拳別人的肚子
I just punched someone in the kidney.
正是在下
It was me.
我知道
I know.
好臭的屁味
Oh, oh, bad smell,
是誰吃了中東蔬菜球啊
Like someone hooked up with a falafel.
-正是在下  -我知道
-It was me. - I know.
-克制點  -抱歉
- Max. - Sorry.
地鐵里  飛機上  舞池中  我任屁自放
Subways, planes, and mosh pits, I let it ride.
我愛死這件上衣干洗后清新的味道了
I love the smell of this fresh, dry-cleaned blouse.
我好興奮我能擺脫那服務生制服
I am so excited to be out of that waitress uniform,
重新穿上我的時尚工裝
and back in my chic business clothes,
然后走進我的辦公室
and, you know, going to my office,
在那里運用著我的沃頓才華
where I'll probably save the day
拯救辦公室於水火之中
using some of my Wharton magic.
我更喜歡你內心希望全滅的樣子
You know, I think I like you better without hope.
麥克斯  你知道這學校學費很貴吧
Max, you know this school is expensive, right?
你會抱著積極心態去上課吧
You're going in with a good attitude, right?
不是啊  不然厄爾的"鉛筆盒"是干啥用的
No, that's what Earl's pencils are for.
別擔心啦  我會盡力
Don't worry, I'll do my best.
你看  這次我有個書包呢
I mean, look, I have a book bag.
以前我去上學  我媽唯一給我帶的東西
The only thing my mother ever sent me to school with
就是張寫了"幫忙檢查虱子"的字條
was a note that said "Check me for lice."
大家送你書包真是太貼心了
It was so sweet of everyone to give you that,
雖然這害我一整晚睡不著
even though I didn't sleep all night about it.
而且看起來不便宜呢
And it looks kind of expensive.
看看是什么牌子的
Check for a designer label.
何必呢  心意最重要嘛
Why? It's the thought that counts.
胡說八道
Since when?
讓我看看
Let me see it.
第二大道站
Second avenue station.
這里是第二大道站
This is second avenue.
慘了  麥克斯
No, no, no, Max!
他搶到了書包  很好  麥克斯
No, he got the book bag. Good, Max, good.
千萬別放手
Don't let go.
萬一車子發動了
What if the train starts to leave
然后我手斷了咋辦
and my arms pop off?
我還怎么去上烘焙學校啊
How will I go to pastry school?
我就得跟那些殘疾用嘴來
I'll be one of those people decorating cookies
裝飾餅干的人一樣了
with a bag in their mouth.
你是個魔鬼
You are the devil.
魔鬼
The devil.
你就是個渣渣
You have nothing.
拉  麥克斯  快拉  從魔鬼手上拉走
Pull, Max, pull! Pull it from the devil!
拉不走啊  這魔鬼有健身
Can't. The devil works out.
我的書包
My bag.
我的襯衫
My blouse.
我的大麻
My weed.
這下好了  都開始上課了
Oh, great, look. Class has started.
我的新生活已經搞砸了
My new life already blows.
帥氣大廚在里面呢
Oh, look. There's Chef gorgeous.
我不想讓他看到我這么狼狽
I don't want him to see me like this.
我去洗手間看看
I'm gonna go to the restroom and see
能不能用冷水把這臟污弄掉
if cold water can get out any of the stain.
-快進去上課  -可是我的廚師服跟書包沒了
- Go, Max. - But I don't have my chef coat or book bag.
我知道它們只在我生命中存在過几小時
I know I only had them for a couple of hours,
但那是我最美好的時光
but it was the best part of me.
你能行的
You'll do great.
先幫我個忙  檢查我有沒有虱子
First, do me a favor. Check me for lice.
這門課是設計來向你們介紹
This course is designed to introduce you
一些技朮與技巧
to the skills and techniques required
來制作如發面面包
in the production of yeast bread,
酥皮面團  奶黃餅  泡芙
short pastry doughs, custards, pate a choux,
以及蛋糕糊等等
and cake batters.
麥克斯大廚  你遲到了
Chef Max, you are late.
你確定課不是10點17分開始嗎
Wait, are sure class doesn't start at 10:17?
對不起  我在地鐵上被混蛋給搶劫了
Sorry, I got robbed on the subway by some jerk.
喂喂喂  干嘛指鼻子罵我
Hey, hey, hey, I'm right here.
我沒錢走投無路
I ran out of options, and I didn't wanna
又不想跳脫衣舞賺學費  所以...
strip my way through pastry school.
可以靠脫衣舞賺學費嗎
That's an option?
好了  廚師們  專心點
All right, Chefs. Let's focus.
他剛是說他想"搞我們"[專心]嗎
Did he say he wants to "foke us"?
越洗越糟了
早安啊  碧碧
Morning, Bebe.
天啊  你這是怎么了
Hi. Oh, my God. What happened to you?
我先提醒你  我的醫生說
And I should tell you my doctor says
我接下來一個月內都不應該聽到壞消息
I'm not allowed to hear bad news for another month.
抱歉我這么狼狽來上班
I apologize for my appearance.
但我們在地鐵上被搶了
We got robbed on the subway,
然后被拿著熱咖啡的人弄了一身
and then someone hit me with hot coffee.
然后我去用了冷水想洗掉咖啡漬
Then, I went to wash cold water on the stain
結果沒洗掉  還弄得像要參加
and somehow wound up entering myself
性感"濕身"選美賽了
in a wet t-shirt contest.
負面能量太多我扛不住
Um, that's a lot of energy for me,
先讓我坐在位子上休息
So I'm just gonna need to sit here
然后平靜一會吧
for a second and be quiet.
我知道我現在該讓你平靜  我也支持
I know we're being quiet, which I'm all about,
好可愛的小狗啊
but cute dogs.
謝謝  這是可卡犬
Oh, thanks. They're cocker spaniels.
我拯救了他們
I rescue them.
大家都想著去拯救灰狗  斗牛犬啊
You know, people rescue greyhounds and pit bulls,
但都沒人想到可卡也需要拯救
but everyone ignores the cocker spaniel.
都覺得可卡犬惡心  要宰了他們
They're like, "Ew, eye goo. Shoot it."
我養了三只可卡[三根雞雞]
I have three cockers.
你有寵物嗎
Do you have any pets?
有匹馬  叫栗寶
I have a horse, Chestnut.
他是只純種馬
He's a thoroughbred.
我該從哪里開始幫忙呢
Well, what can I do first?
這是什么  為什么給了我果汁菜單
What's this? Why am I holding a juice menu?
每天我們都為所有學生與員工
Every day, we get fresh-pressed juice
買新鮮的鮮榨果汁
for the students and the staff.
太享受了
What a treat.
新鮮果汁是純騙錢的
Fresh juice is such a scam
但是別人請的就不算
unless someone else is payin'.
我要一杯綠色三號
I'll take the greens number three.
好的  寫上單子
Uh-huh, well, put it on the list
然后去問別人要喝什么吧
when you get the other ones.
等等  所以是我得去買果汁嗎
Wait, I'm supposed to get the juice?
我就是壞消息集中地
Oh, boy, it's like I'm a bad news machine.
沒關系
Okay.
樂意效勞  沒意料到  但很樂意幫忙
Happy to do it. Surprised, but happy.
那我可以借一套那可愛的廚師服穿穿嗎
Uh, maybe I could change into one of those cute Chef jackets.
尼可拉斯大廚規定了只有烘焙廚師能穿
Oh, Chef Nicholas only permits pastry Chefs to wear these.
但我不能第一天就這么狼狽的出場吧
But I can't meet everyone on my first day looking like this.
當買果汁的人已經夠慘了吧
I mean, it's already bad enough I'm the juice girl.
我有一些健身衣服可以給你穿
I have some workout clothes you can wear.
你放心  我一次都還沒穿過
Don't worry. I haven't worn them yet.
但總有一天會穿的
But I will someday.
你們好  大家好啊
Hi. Hi, everyone.
我是來問你們喝什么鮮果汁
I'm here to take the fresh juice orders
也順便說一聲  我本來上班穿的不是這個
and also to say this is not what I came to work in.
我穿的衣服可沒瞪著大眼的狗頭
What I came to work in had less eyes.
卡洛琳  歡迎你
Caroline, welcome.
-在辦公室干得怎么樣  -很好
- How is it going in the office so far? - So great,
我今天真不是穿這個來上班
and so not what I came to work in.
通常我穿的都是香奈兒  而不是犬衣
I'm usually wearing Chanel, not le chien.
那是法語"狗"的意思
That's "dog" in French.
那也是英語"二"的意思
Oh, 'cause it's "dork" in English.
很高興見到你們倆
Well, it is lovely to see both of your faces.
同學  我們先從基本的開始
Class, we start with the basics.
不  不  后面的同學
No, no, no, you in the back--
喝果汁嗎  小姐  想從一個
Juice, miss? Care for a juice
高考成績1560分的人那點果汁嗎[舊制滿分1600]
from someone who scored 1560 on her SATs?
你居然考超過500分
You can score more than 500?
你干嘛要穿這件衣服啊
Why the hell are you wearing that?
這讓你的胸部顯得更平更悲哀
I didn't think your chest could get any sadder.
這是碧碧的衣服
It's Bebe's.
麥克斯  我來這工作不是幫人點果汁的
Max, taking juice orders is not what I came here to do.
我懂你意思  我點一杯寶石紅
I hear you. I'll have the ruby red.
我總是保持花嘴干淨[龜頭]
I always keep the edge clean,
這樣當我擠[射]的時候
So when I'm squeezing it,
奶油[精液]就不會噴得哪兒都是了
It's not gonna have cream popping all over the place.
警世良言啊
Words to live by.
可惜我恰恰相反
I have the opposite problem.
瞧  我的"奶油"噴涌而出
Yo, my cream's poppin' right now.
你這是干嘛
What are you doing?
你答應過我會認真上課的
You told me you were gonna take school seriously.
不能怪我  是那家伙帶壞我
It's not me. That guy's a bad influence.
你看他
Look at him.
他長得就像芝麻街卡通里買毒品的人
He looks like someone who sells drugs on Sesame Street.
你敢玩出火就殺了你
You're gonna get in trouble,
我犧牲穿可卡犬衣服
and I am not wearing a cocker spaniel
可不是為了看你被踢出去
so you can get kicked out of class.
好  我知道了
Right. I hear you.
話說我的果汁呢
Now, where's my juice?
麥克斯大廚  快看我的獨家技能
Hey, Chef Max. Check out my technique.
超棒超惡心的聲音
Awesome gross sound bonus.
大廚  你要覺得這樣玩很有意思
Chef, if you find this so funny,
不如你出去跟"五指"姑娘玩吧
why don't you take a fiver?
反正你不就愛說這些嗎
Isn't this how your saying goes?
我沒愛說這些
I don't have a saying,
但如果我有  那應該是
but if I did, it'd be more like
"口交不算偷吃"
"Eatin' ain't cheatin'."
如果有人覺得有東西很好笑
Anyone else who finds something hilarious
可以跟他一起去走廊
can also go into the hall.
-麥克斯大廚  -不用了  一點都不好笑
- Chef Max? - Nope, nothing 'ilarious.
繼續上課吧
Teach on.
不許再開黃腔了
Enough with the dirty jokes.
我們來這的目的是成為優秀的面包師[自慰師]
We are all here to become master bakers.
我在掌握烘焙[自慰]這方面可是下了不少[硬]功夫
Master-baking is something I work really hard at it.
-要成為一名優秀的烘焙師  -我自己去走廊吧
- To be a master baker--  - I'll be in the hall.
-我是迪克  -你剛是說自己是"怪胎"嗎
- Hi, I'm Deke. - Did you say "Freak?"
-是迪克  -是"怪咖"嗎
- Deke. - Did you say "Geek?"
大"鳥"迪克的迪克
Deke, as in "Big Deke."
我的更大
Mine's bigger.
我們應該成為搭檔
We should be lab partners.
來嘛  這組合超棒的
Come on. It'll be bitchin'.
超大號[麥克斯]大鳥  一起做蛋糕
Max and Deke, making cakes.
周日  周日  周日
Sunday, Sunday, Sunday,
主義樂團要為我們帶來特別演出
with a special performance by Creed.
好了  別玩了  別玩了
Okay, now stop, stop, stop.
我在努力當個好學生
I am trying to be a good student,
所以你離我遠點
so you just stay away from me.
你會帶壞我的
You are a bad influence.
我這番話肯定超順  因為小時候
And I know I nailed that speech 'cause kids at school
同學們總對我說這番話
used to say it to me all the time.
-到時間換衛生棉了嗎  -是的
- Time to change your tampon? - Yep.
經期第二天  流量超大
Day two. Serious flow.
腰包真可愛  你的最炫民族風披肩在哪里
Killer fanny pack. Where's your tribal poncho?
那是用來放針的
Ah, keep my needles in this.
你居然還是個癮君子
You're a drug addict too?
天啊  想不跟你一起混真難
God. You are irresistible.
是用來打胰島素的  我是個糖尿病患
It's--it's insulin. I'm a diabetic.
一個患有糖尿病的甜點大廚
A diabetic pastry Chef.
你的自毀傾向比我的強多了
Wow, you're even more self-destructive than me.
糖尿病  什么感覺啊
So diabetes, how is that?
很沒勁  我寧可得梅毒
Disappointing. I put in for syphilis.
別笑了  老娘要穿著這衣服
Stop laughing. I have to carry 27 juices
去兩個街區外扛27杯果汁
2 blocks wearing this.
你干嘛讓狗頭女這樣跟你說話啊
Why'd you let the dog lady talk to you like that?
即使穿著那件傻逼衣服  她還是我的朋友
She's my friend, even in that shirt.
又花了我12塊錢
Well, there goes another $12.
我干洗這件襯衫的錢
I have spent more money dry cleaning this blouse
比我健康保險上花的錢還多
than I have on health care.
健保  你是說我們從9毛9店
Health care? You mean that box of band-aids
買回來的那一盒子止血貼吧
We got at the 99 cent store?
我明天一定要漂漂亮亮地去上班
I just have to look good tomorrow.
今天太丟臉了
Today was mortifying.
我被果汁店員叫"倒霉狗"
They called me "sad dog" at the juice place.
"倒霉狗  你的果汁好了"
"Sad dog, your juices are ready."
倒霉狗  上菜了
Sad dog, pick up.
你能拿去十號桌嗎  我在照看卡座區
Can you take these to table ten? I'm backed up on the booths.
你去吧  我要坐在這休息一會
Can you? I'm kind of just sitting here a minute,
享受不被人使喚的美好時光
enjoying not being told what to do.
我在那間學校真是受夠了
I get enough of it at that school.
聽著
Look.
如果你要學人老媽使喚小孩  學像點
If you're gonna do the mother thing, do it right.
把你的手伸進油鍋  或更慘一點
Stick your hand in boiling oil or even more painful,
狂看精彩電視台的《日落沙哈》
binge-watch Shahs of Sunset on Bravo.
講述加州比佛利山的伊朗裔美國人如何
在種族傳統和美國現代文化之間尋找平衡的故事
現在就進廚房  我有話跟你說
I need to talk to you in the kitchen now.
出去  有人准備因為培訓的事而被訓
Leave, someone's about to get schooled about school.
貌似場面會變得丑陋不堪[淫穢下流]
This looks like it's going to get dirty and ugly.
我可以錄下來嗎
May I film it?
如果可以錄  我能放到網上賣嗎
And if so, may I then sell it on the internet?
聽著  你這么做不能只是為了我
Look. You can't just do this for me.
-說得對  那我們退學嗎  -當然不行
- You're right. So we're out? - No, we're not out,
你說過你會為我這么做的
you said you were gonna do this for me.
我知道  可你剛不是說
I know, but you just said
我不能為了你才這么做嗎
I can't just do it for you,
我覺得你說得對
And I agree.
-我的意思是  我騙誰啊  -我啊
- I mean, who was I kidding? - Me.
你騙我
You were kidding me.
我去那里上班是想施展我的商業才能
I went in there thinking I was gonna use my business skills,
而我曾經希望跟法國佬
and whatever hope I had of a flirtation
調情賣騷現在也沒戲了
with Frenchie McFrench went out the window
因為他看見我穿著那件T恤  上面寫著
when he saw me wearing that T-shirt that said,
"記得節育  勿忘閹割"
"Don't forget to spay and neuter me."
好吧  我退學  沒關系
Fine, I can quit. It's fine.
-真的嗎  -假的  當然有關系啦
- It is? Really? - No, it's not fine.
-我騙誰啊  -我啊  你騙我
- Who am I kidding? - Me. You were kidding me.
你一定要在那里找到
Well, you've gotta figure out something
能讓你保持興趣的東西
there to keep you interested,
因為你去烘焙學校不能只是為了我
because you can't go to pastry school just for me,
而我也不會為了你而退學
and I'm not gonna not go to pastry school for you.
好吧  你說得對  麥克斯
Okay. You're right, Max.
我當然會為你這么做
Of course I'll do it for you.
我只是今天過得很糟糕
I just had a bad day.
我們都是
I mean, we both did.
你丟了書包和大麻
You lost your man's briefcase and your drugs,
而我丟了自尊和可能有的小戀情
and I lost my dignity and a possible love interest.
驚喜吧
Surprise!
瞧  驚喜就應該是這樣
See, that's how it's supposed to go.
我們給你買了個新書包
We got you a new book bag.
一套新的大廚制服
Yeah, and a new Chef's jacket.
還有一把彈簧刀
And a switchblade.
對啊  因為我們不想再買第三套大廚服了
Yeah, 'cause we're not buyin' another Chef's jacket.
麥克斯  你知道這意味著什么嗎
Max, you know what this means?
我得到兩次驚喜禮物  而你毛都沒有嗎
That I got two surprises, and you got nothing?
不  在學校一切都會好的
No, that everything's gonna work out at that school.
我是說  眨眼之間
I mean, in the blink of an eye,
就像這樣  事情可以由壞變好
just like this, things can change from bad to good.
也不算完全變好
Well, not totally good.
我依舊毛都沒有
They still haven't gotten me anything.
卡洛琳  有你的禮物
Caroline, you didn't not get anything.
給  你專屬的鉛筆盒
Here, your very own pencil case.
但沒"鉛筆"  我的"鉛筆"供貨商被抓了
But no pencils. My pencil dealer got busted.
謝謝你們  我感動死了
Thank you, guys. I'm touched.
真是萬萬沒想到啊
I was not expecting it.
是嗎  你可是拿一哭二鬧三上吊來強迫我們
Really? 'cause you kinda bullied us all into it.
我的SAT成績語言成績是780分
So that's a 780 on verbal,
數學成績也是780分
and a 780 on math.
而且我拿的是金融學位
And with my degree in Finance,
在市里跑來跑去買果汁這種事
jackass-ing around the city getting juice
完全是在浪費我的天賦啊
could be seen as a waste of my talents.
我畢業典禮時的優秀學生代表說過
And as the valedictorian at my graduation said--
也就是我自己說過
and I'm stealin' from myself here,
"我看見了金融界的未來
"I've seen the future of Finance,
也就是我們"
and it's us."
所以你是想讓我去買果汁嗎
So you want me to get the juices?
就今天  拜托了
Just for today. Please?
法式蛋白乾是練習
Meringue cookies are a simple way
裱花袋技巧的最簡單的方法
to practice our pastry bag technique.
真是個有趣的技巧啊  大廚
Hm, interesting technique you got going there, Chef.
伙計  我們得拋棄彼此的無聊搭檔
Dude, we gotta ditch these deadbeat partners.
我被一位老奶奶拖累
I'm stuck over there with grandma.
不要  我不想換掉我旁邊的大胖子
No, I'm staying with the big guy next to me.
他才不會讓我惹麻煩
He's not gonna get me in trouble.
他從不說話  快走開
He never talks. Get outta here.
回到你的桌子上去  胖子阿伯特
Go back to your own table, Fat Albert.
《胖子阿伯特》是美國70年代開始風行的熱門卡通劇集
主角是一名黑胖子
好吧
Okay.
我回去
I'm going back.
但你叫我胖子阿伯特  是因為我是黑人
And the Fat Albert thing was 'cause I'm black,
不是胖  對不對
Not fat, right?
因為我一年怎么也去兩三次健身房吧
'cause I go to the gym two, three times a year.
我聽到前面只有說話聲  沒有干活聲
I hear talking, but no baking up front.
不  不  你聽到的只有干活聲
No, no, no, you only hear baking.
這里在激烈地"干"呢
Just furiously master-baking up here.
蛋白乾要有漂亮的尖角
The meringue needs to have nice peaks.
你們要做出濕濕的尖尖角[乳頭]
You are looking to make moist, pointy peaks.
我最喜歡捏"它們"了
I like to pinch them.
主廚  咱倆私下說一句
Chef, seriously, man-to-man,
有個問題
we got a problem.
我覺得麥克斯不應該跟那個大胖子在一組
I don't think Max should be stuck with that big guy.
他太猥瑣了
He's not cool.
我剛在那邊
I was just over there,
他唯一感興趣的尖尖角在她身上
and the only pointy peaks he's interested in are hers.
我說的是她的咪咪  主廚
Talkin' boobies here, Chef.
約翰大廚  迪克大廚
Chef John, Chef Deke here
似乎覺得你在性騷擾麥克斯
Seems to think you are sexually harassing Max.
拜托喲
Oh, please.
如果人家要性騷擾別人  那人肯定是你
If I was harassing anyone, it would be you, Chef.
你的魅力無法擋嘛
I mean, come on.
馬上回來  姐們兒
Be right back, big Mary.
你真懂我
You know it.
我的果汁呢  都過了一個小時了
Where's my juice? It's been an hour.
情緒波動的精靈去拿了
The mood swing elf's getting them.
聽著  我要進去跟尼古拉斯主廚賣騷
Look, I'm coming in there To flirt with Chef Nicholas,
當我進去的時候  我要你說
and when I enter, I need you to say,
"卡洛琳  你看起來美呆了"
"Caroline, you look amazing."
不行
No.
我的身體不允許我說出這種話
I actually physically can't say that.
我寧愿沖進去大喊
I would rather walk in there and yell,
"我有陰虱  剛剛有三只逃跑了"
"I have crabs, and three of them just escaped."
快叫救護車  快叫救護車
Call 9-1-1. Call 9-1-1.
那個可愛的混血男出事啦
Something's happened to the adorable mixed-race one.
迪克
Deke?
他有糖尿病  他需要打胰島素
He's diabetic. He needs insulin.
這里有人會打針嗎
Has anyone here ever administered a needle?
"打針"就跟"把針插進去"的意思一樣  對吧
Uh, administer means the same thing as "shove it in," right?
很好  很好  麥克斯  你過來
Good, good, good, Max. Come, come, come.
好的  他的注射器在腰包
Okay, uh, his syringes are in his fanny pack.
老實說  我之前干這種事時
I've actually never done this
都得聽著重金屬搖滾樂
without Iron Maiden playing in the background,
但我來打打看吧
But I'll give it a shot.
在我性感的身軀上隨便打一針就行
Just put it anywhere in my hot bod.
上帝保佑
God help us.
我討厭針  我不敢看了
Oh, I hate needles. I can't look.
女士們  別驚慌失措好嗎
Get it together, ladies.
所以醫生不准我抱小孩
This is why I'm not allowed to hold babies.
麥克斯  從現在開始你和迪克一組
Max, I think you and Deke should be lab partners from now on
以防今天的事再次發生
in case something like this happens again.
-沒問題吧  -我別無選擇
- Is that okay? - I guess if I have to.
麥克斯  你呢
Max?
我也別無選擇
I guess if I have to.
你是故意不按時打胰島素嗎
What, did you not take your insulin on purpose?
人家真的很想做你搭檔嘛
I really wanted to be your partner.
碧碧  我在這里找不到大廚上衣
Bebe, I can't find a Chef jacket anywhere in here.
很抱歉  我知道我不應該穿那個
And I'm sorry, I know I'm not supposed to wear one,
但我真的很冷
but I'm really cold,
我不能一天都穿著這身衣服走來走去
and I can't walk around like this all day.
或許我可以幫你
Maybe I can help.
你不能又濕又冷地站著
You can't stand there wet and cold.
-穿我的上衣吧  -不  不
- Take my jacket. - Oh, no, no, no.
不用了  那也行
You don't have-- oh, that'll work.
不好意思我里面沒穿衣服
I'm sorry about the no shirt under,
我上課的時候  總是覺得很熱
but I just get so hot when I'm teaching.
是啊  熱  太熱[性感]了
Yeah, hot. So hot.
我的天啊[法語]
Oh mon dieu.
我正准備[射]給卡洛琳呢
I was just giving it to Caroline.
我是說  她需要換件衣服
I mean, she needs something to wear,
我就把我的給她了
and--and now, she has it.
大廚  晚點見
Chef, I will see you later.
卡洛琳
Caroline.
麥克斯  我我找到讓我性致昂揚的東西了
Max, I think I found something to keep me interested.
這下奇怪了  現在我成了好學生
This is weird. So I'm the good student now?
而你卻成了跟老師上床的那個
And you're the one sleeping with the teacher?
我們又沒上床
We're not sleeping together.
干嘛這么說  你覺得他想要我嗎
Why? Do you think he wants to?
我不知道  但在胖子姐們兒扑過去前
I don't know, but you better hurry it up
你最好早點下手
before big Mary gets him.